[
	{
		"title": "Traffic stop questions",
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "Hello, how are you?",
				"answers": ["Hey!", "Hello officer.", "Good day.", "Hello.", "Can I help you?", "*Says nothing*", "What do you want?", "I don't have time for this."]
			},
			{
				"question": "Where are you heading to?",
				"answers": ["I'm going home.", "It's my own business...", "A friends house.", "Fuck off.", "*Says nothing*"]
			},
			{
				"question": "Where are you coming from?",
				"answers": ["I'm going home.", "It's my own business...", "A friends house.", "Fuck off.", "*Says nothing*"]
			},
			{
				"question": "Have you had any alcohol recently?",
				"answers": ["Yes.", "*Says nothing*", "No.","No.","No.","No.", "Of course I did.", "Absolutly not!", "Nope.", "Fuck off.", "Why?", "I'd rather not say.", "I plead the fifth.", "*Says nothing*"]
			},
			{
				"question": "Have you taken any drugs recently?",
				"answers": ["Yes.", "*Says nothing*", "No.","No.","No.","No.", "Of course I did.", "Absolutly not!", "Nope.", "Fuck off.", "Why?", "I'd rather not say.", "I plead the fifth.", "*Says nothing*"]
			},
			{
				"question": "Why did you commit that traffic infringement?",
				"answers": ["I didn't see it.", "I am late for work.", "I am late to a party.", "I didn't see you there.", "I do that all the time!", "I didn't break any laws!", "Fuck you.", "*Says nothing*"]
			},
			{
				"question": "Is there anything illegal in the vehicle?",
				"answers": ["*Laughs*", "Fuck you.", "*Says nothing*", "Nope.", "No.", "I hope not.", "Not that I know of.", "Not since the last time I checked."]
			},
			{
				"question": "Mind if I search your vehicle?",
				"answers": ["Yes, I mind.", "I'd rather you didn't", "I guess so.", "It's not my car.", "Absolutly not.", "Absolutly! I have nothing to hide!"]
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"title": "Pedestrian Questions",
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "Hello, how are you?",
				"answers": ["Hey!", "Hello officer.", "Good day.", "Hello.", "Can I help you?", "*Says nothing*", "What do you want?", "I don't have time for this."]
			},
			{
				"question": "Where are you heading to?",
				"answers": ["I'm going home.", "It's my own business...", "A friends house.", "Fuck off.", "*Says nothing*"]
			},
			{
				"question": "Where are you coming from?",
				"answers": ["I'm going home.", "It's my own business...", "A friends house.", "Fuck off.", "*Says nothing*"]
			},
			{
				"question": "Have you had any alcohol recently?",
				"answers": ["Yes.", "*Says nothing*", "No.","No.","No.","No.", "Of course I did.", "Absolutly not!", "Nope.", "Fuck off.", "Why?", "I'd rather not say.", "I plead the fifth.", "*Says nothing*"]
			},
			{
				"question": "Have you taken any drugs recently?",
				"answers": ["Yes.", "*Says nothing*", "No.","No.","No.","No.", "Of course I did.", "Absolutly not!", "Nope.", "Fuck off.", "Why?", "I'd rather not say.", "I plead the fifth.", "*Says nothing*"]
			}
		]
	}
	
]